So we can visit the checkout page, on the checkout page let's make the buttons which are part of
Bu yzden check-out sayfasndaki check-out sayfasnda, hangi iptal ve devam ettirmek
CheckoutSummary work,the cancel and continue button.
iin zet ii kontrol etmenin bir paras olan dmeleri yapalm.
Now these buttons are of course in the CheckoutSummary, I could handle them there by turning it into
imdi bu dmeler elbette onlara bir snfa evirerek onlar halledebilecekleri
a class but I just want to expose this event basically in a checkout container which wraps the
zet ak zetinde ancak bu olay temelde, kullanm zetini kullanarak kontrol zet bileenini tamamlayan bir kontrol konteyneri iine
CheckoutSummary component by using this good old approach of using props and then any props I expect to get
sergilemek istiyorum sahne ve daha sonra herhangi bir sahne bir tklama zerine
the reference to the method which should be executed upon a click at.
yrtlmesi gereken yntem iin bavuru almak iin bekliyoruz.
So here I will name is
Yani burada isim koyacam.
onCheckoutCancelled or just CheckoutCancelled to be in line with my previous namings and then here,
veya sadece kontrol edin nceki adlarm dorultusunda olamaz ve daha sonra sahne kontrol devam etti.
propsCheckoutContinued.
Kontrol d brakn
Now I need to implement these props when using the CheckoutSummary component
imdi kontrol zet bileeni kullanrken bu sahne uygulamak gerekiyor.
so there I don't only pass ingredients, I also have CheckoutCancelled and I have CheckoutContinued.
Yani orada sadece geip bitmeyen okumalar okudum ve iptal edilmitim ve kontrol ettim devam ettim.
Now I need methods which do something upon each of the two, I'll add a
imdi her iki tarafn zerine bir eyler yapacak herhangi bir yntem ekleyeceim.
checkoutCancelledHandler which is a method which should do something and I'll use this method syntax
Bir ey yapmas gereken bir yntem olan iptal edilen ileyiciyi kontrol edin ve orada
to be able to use the this keyword inside of there and checkoutContinuedHandler which should also
bu anahtar kelimeyi kullanabilmek iin bu yntem szdizimini kullanacam ve ayrca bakmas gereken devam eden ileyiciyi
look like that.
kontrol edin.
Now since I'm in the checkout container which was loaded with the route component, we here also have
eriimi var Propp da iptal edildiinde yrtmek istediim geri dn yntemine sahip.
access to this props and there too, the history prop, and the history prop also has a go back method
imdi rota bileeni ile yklenen kontrol konteynrndayken, burada da bu sahnelere ve
which I want to execute upon cancelling.
gemite Propp'a ve gemie
This simply goes back to the last page, in the other case here where I want to continue, I'll use replace
Bu sadece Arrow durumundaki son sayfaya gider ve buradaki tm kullanm yerine
instead to replace the current route with checkout/contactData for example. We don't handle this
devam etmek istiyorum, bunun yerine geerli rotay deitirmek iin eik izgi konta verisi ile deitirelim; rnein bu
path yet but this should be the path which soon loads the contactData component which we don't have
blm henz ele almamakla birlikte bu, ksa srede sahip olmadmz iletiim verileri
yet again.
bileenini ykledi.
Now we need to hook these handlers up so down there,
imdi bu ileyicileri oraya sktrmamz gerekiyor.
This CheckoutCancelledHandler and does checkoutContinuedHandler should be used,
Bu, iptal edilen ileyiciyi kontrol eder ve devam eden ileyici kullanlmaya allmasn kontrol eder.
save all the files and now let's try this out on
Tm yanllar saklayn ve imdi bunu deneyelim.
checkout. If I click on cancel and take it back to my burger builder
ptal etmeyi tklatp tklamadm kontrol edin ve Bergrin reticisine geri gtrn.
let me go back to checking out, if I click Continue,
Devam Et'i tklarsam kontrol etmeye devam edeyim.
You'll see URL changes but of course that doesn't do anything because we're not handling it yet
Deiikliklerinizi grrsnz, ancak elbette ki hibir ey yapmaz nk henz ileme koymuyoruz.
so this is something I will have to handle in the future.
Bu gelecekte stesinden geleceim bir ey.
The thing I want to do before handling that though is that I want to render the burger I really built
Borcu ele almadan nce yapmak istediim ey, gerekten kurduum burgeri deil, baz
and not some arbitrary burger here. To render the burger
keyfi burgerleri burger sunmak iin burada yapmak istiyorum.
I actually built, I will have to pass the respective data about my burger to the checkout page.
Aslnda bultum, burgerim ile ilgili verileri deme sayfasna iletmek zorunda kalacam.
So from the burger builder here. There I build some burger and if I now click order now and continue,
Yani burada Bergere Boulder'dan baz burger yapyorum ve u anda sipari veriyorum ve
I need to pass data about ingredients onto the checkout page. This is the next goal, pass the data on
devam edersem malzemelerle ilgili verileri verilerin tesine geen k sayfas felaketine gelecek nesnelere geirmem gerekiyor.
I want to pass it on while a query parent is here. Again feel free to implement this on your own,
Bunu neden bir sorgu ebeveyninin tekrar kendi banza uygulamakta zgrdn anlatmak isterim.
you learned everything you need for this over the last module, we'll do it together in the next lecture.
Bir sonraki dersin son modl birlikte yapaca gn boyunca ihtiyacnz olan her eyi renirsiniz.